A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, [1961] 1970-1971
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: General Files, 1970-1971
  - Special Programs (Elwood) 1970-1971 (Box 56)
  - Special Assistant to President, Names for 1970-1971 (Box 56)
  - Speeches 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - Speech and Drama 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - Sponsored Programs 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - State Board of Education 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - State Council of Higher Education - Presentation at Biennial Visit, 4 March 1971 1970-1971 (Box 57)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1970-1971 (Box 58)
  - State Department of Education 1970-1971 (Box 59)
  - Student Affairs 1970-1971 (Box 59)
  - Student First-Year Council Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 60)
  - Student Aid Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 60)
  - Student Council 1970-1971 (Box 60)
  - Student Council Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 61)
  - Student Counseling Center 1970-1971 (Box 61)
  - Student Health Department 1970-1971 (Box 61)
  - Student Legal Forum 1970-1971 (Box 61)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 61)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1970-1971 (Box 61)
  - Traffic Control 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - Transportation and Safety (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - Treasurer 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - Tuition and Fees 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - "U" 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - United Givers Fund - 1970 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - United Givers Fund - 1971 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - UNESCO 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - U. S. Department of Agriculture 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - U. S. Army Foreign Science and Technology Center 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - U. S. Congress 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - U. S. Department of Defense 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare 1970-1971 (Box 62)
  - U. S. Department of State 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - U. S. Naval Academy 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Center in Virginia 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Editor 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Events 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Hall 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Houses (general) 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Printing Office 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Press of Virginia 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Relations 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - Universities Research Association 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Topics 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - University Union 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - Upward Bound 1970-1971 (Box 63)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Weekly 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Visitors - General 1970-1971 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Blandy Farm 1970-1971 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Building and Grounds Committee and Finance 1970-1971 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Education Policy Committee 1970-1971 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Executive Committee 1970-1971 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Finance Committee 1970-1971 (Box 65)
  - Visitors - Mary Washington College 1970-1971 (Box 66)
  - Visitors - Medical Committee 1970-1971 (Box 66)
  - Visitors - Student Affairs and Athletics Committee 1970-1971 (Box 66)
  - Visitors - Docket, 2 October 1970 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 2 October 1970 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Docket, 4 December 1970 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 4 December 1970 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Docket, 13 February 1971 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 13 February 1971 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Docket, 3 April 1971 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 3 April 1971 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Docket, 4 June 1971 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 4 June 1971 1970-1971 (Box 67)
  - "W - Wh" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 68)
  - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 68)
  - Walpole Society 1970-1971 (Box 68)
  - Washington Hall, Restoration of 1970-1971 (Box 68)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1970-1971 (Box 68)
  - Water Pollution Control Lab. 1970-1971 (Box 68)
  - Water Resources 1970-1971 (Box 68)
  - "X" - "Y" - "Z" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 68)
- Series II: University Committees, 1969-1971
  - Administrative 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Admissions 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Arboretum 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Architectural Advisory Committee 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Athletic Advisory Council (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Bayly Museum 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Calendar of Events 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Calendar and Scheduling 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Catalogue 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Chapel 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Communications 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Community Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Danforth Fellowships 1970-1971 (Box 69)
  - Educational and Employment Opportunities, Obligations, and Rights 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Data Processing 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Foreign Students 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Fraternities 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Fulbright Grants 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Graduate (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Graduate Awards and Recruiting (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Graphics 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Gwathmey Award 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Housing 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Institutional Analysis 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1970-1971 (Box 70)
  - Lectures: Special Lectures 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Library 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Page - Barbour and Richard 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Madison Papers 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Master Plan 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Names 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Processions 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Public Occasions 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Radiation Safety 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Registration 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Research and Sponsored Programs 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Rhodes Scholarships 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - ROTC 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Scientific Computer Users' 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Loans, and Employment 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Security and General Safety 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Student Activities 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Summer Grants 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Traffic Appeals 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Traffic Control 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - University Committee on Students 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - University Environment 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - University Union 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1970-1971 (Box 71)
  - Special Committee - George Mason College Student Union Building 1969-1971 (Box 72)
  - Special Committee - George Mason College Educational Planning for 1969-1970 (Box 72)
  - Ad hoc Committee - Search for Dean, Graduate School of Business 1970-1971 (Box 72)
  - Ad hoc Committee - Selection of Dean of Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1970-1971 (Box 72)
  - Ad hoc Committee - Vice-President for Medical Affairs 1970-1971 (Box 72)
  - Special Committee - Gym - Auditorium: Patrick Henry 1970-1971 (Box 72)
- Series III: Miscellaneous Files, 1961-1971
  - Gus Hall 1970-1971 (Box 73)
  - Radio Committee 1961-1962 (Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence of several years 1970-1971 (Box 73)
  - Selective Service System 1967-1969 (Box 73)